ladies and gentlemen Kelsey
[Applause]
car oh man what is up
Madison thank thank you guys so much for
coming out tonight I'm so excited to be
here uh people have been asking me why I
decided to shoot this special in
Wisconsin and it's because I think
everybody here has a resting blood
alcohol of
[Applause]
0.12 ah there it is there it is that's
good for comedy yeah you guys seem so
happy
here just slam and cheese
curs I love it you try to shoot a
special in La everybody's intermittent
fasting I feel like intermittent fasting
means something different in the
midwest I feel like that's when you guys
black out by 5 and forget to eat
dinner you just wake up the next morning
like I feel good
I wrapped my car around a pole last
night but I feel
fit
mean I thought it' also be fun to shoot
it here since I'm now also a
midwesterner thank you yeah I moved to
Minnesota last year in the month of
January and that's how you die
eight-month Winters are [\h__\h]
brutal God when I hit my onee mark of
living there some of my friends were
like oh how did you celebrate I was like
I just walked into my bathroom like it
was a prison cell and etched one
tally I did learn a lot by moving there
then I learned that God forbid you try
using e there in the winter
that water feels like local
anesthesia did not feel my bee hole for
months it's such a weird state right
when I moved there I turned on the TV
and there were commercials for vacations
to
Alaska and that's when I knew I [\h__\h]
up I was like oh these are broken people
if Alaska is their
Cancun living in Minnesota and going on
vacation to Alaska is like owning a
Nissan Sentra and going on vacation and
renting a Nissan
Sentra that's the same terrible
[\h__\h] I moved there to live with my
boyfriend so that's why I did it in
January because winter sucks it's better
when there's somebody inside
you thank you one horny
woman I appreciate
you Minnesota was a tough sell though I
found out also when I got there that
they have some of the highest state
taxes I was like for
why you're cold and expensive that's
like a dog who's ugly and bites
put it
down let's get out of here
scaddle and I moved there from
Washington where there are no state
taxes so now anytime my boyfriend tries
to start a fight with me I'm like oh let
me remind you that being your girlfriend
now costs me $38 a
day your dick is a very expensive toll
road
let me set the thermostat to 72 [\h__\h]
off let's pick our battles
today when he and I got together we had
that conversation about labels cuz I
felt ready to be called boyfriend and
girlfriend and he goes ah you know being
in my 40s I feel like I'm a little old
to be called somebody's boyfriend but if
you call me your manf
friend sounds like I'm not allowed in
your playground
I was like all right well what are you
going to call me and he goes I'll just
be like this is my
lady I was like well we're not at a
Renaissance
Fair so
no also I can't use the equivalent of
that I can't be like Mom Dad I'd like
you to meet my Lord
and he's also a comedian my ex-husband
was actually a comedian too I can't stop
[\h__\h] where I eat to tell you my love
life is a
Chipotle just keep the eating and
[\h__\h] all Under One
Roof it's very convenient very farmed to
table you
know they're right there
and I wasn't much of a jealous
girlfriend in my 20s but then some
switch flipped in my 30s and now when I
see somebody hit on the person I'm with
I just feel myself anamorph into the
cast of Jersey
short I am ready to brawl and he does
get hit on when he walks on stage women
whistle at him and at comedy clubs
there's usually a security guard in the
back to kick people out in case they
Heckle so at his shows I've just started
to stand next to the security guard
and if I see a woman laughing too hard
at one of his
jokes I just walk up and I'm like hey
I'm going to have to ask you to
leave he's my favorite comedian well
he's my
Lord scoot beat
it I feel like most people assume I'm
exaggerating during that joke but if you
follow me online you'll know I posted a
video a few months ago of a woman who
sat in the front row of one of my shows
and after I told that joke she goes your
boyfriend is my favorite comedian we've
seen him like eight times and I was like
lady did you not just hear that this is
when I go Snookie on
somebody you doing and she doubled down
she's like he's so cute he's so hot and
he responds to my Instagram comments
and that's when I took out my hoop
earrings all the men in the crowd were
looking around like Jerry Jerry
Jerry it's like yeah time to [\h__\h] around
and find out Madam get up here I don't
actually worry about my boyfriend
cheating on me I feel like men's bodies
start to really turn on them in their
40s he has to wake up every 2 hours in
the night to pee and when I see him in
the morning with bags under his eyes I
hug him and I go ah babe I'm sorry you
didn't sleep well and then I think
you're too exhausted to cheat on
me you're not getting enough REM to pull
off two
relationships I like you slow like
this can catch you if I need
to get back here
but now the second I see him start to
reach for melatonin and I'm like the
[\h__\h] are you resting up for
huh you stay
sleepy I don't usually mind our age Gap
but there is that new filter on Tik Tok
where couples are posting pictures
together and then a filter goes across
the screen and it shows you what you'll
look like together in 50 years like it
ages you so I did that with a picture of
me and my boyfriend and when the filter
went across the screen it just made him
disappear it was just me holding an N I
was like
what no
please my boyfriend was like I want to
see the pictur of like oh my phone
died and so did
you what am I going to
do he does hate that he looks older than
me he's been trying to get me to look
older
faster think he wants to like microwave
my
face on my birthday as a prank he hit
all of my expensive skin creams and when
I opened my bathroom cupboard there was
just a pack of
cigarettes got tanning bed
coupon well careful what you wish for
you going to wake up next to Mick
Jagger I have been telling my single
friends that they should date somebody
older than them it's the best they got
their lives together they're financially
secure my boyfriend has a lake cabin you
think I give a [\h__\h] that he has a fake
hip I
don't I don't need somebody to be able
to jump rope to get me wet
I'm riding on a jet ski I'm coming five
times on that thing
anyway my boyfriend shows me his credit
score while we're on the jet ski I'm
like oh my
God our neighbors are like w look at all
the water coming off that
thing like that's not water Diane
that's all me
baby happy
fourth peace be with
you I will say if you date somebody
older than you sometimes people think
you have daddy issues and uh they're
right my dad was an international yo-yo
man for a
living that sentence should not even
exist
I don't know if when you were growing up
a guy came to your school and did yo-yo
demonstrations yeah that's the man who
made
me that's not
great I do love my dad I think he gave
me a very specific amount of daddy
issues like I have enough to have become
a comedian but not enough to have an
only
fans my dad's just a little too
supportive for me to have one of those
if I try to post my boobs on online
behind a pay wall and posted some link
that was like for my biggest fans only
my dad would read that and go I'm
obviously my daughter's biggest fan oh
God
no
Noy
Evelyn I don't know of that many people
personally who are on only fans or in
the porn space I do know of Adriana Chic
I follow her on Twitter because she
tweets the most outrageous things and
they make me laugh so hard she tweeted
the other day and said on my way to the
dentist he has no idea how many
different people's DNA he's about to
clean out of my
[Laughter]
teeth and I say some dirty things up
here but I read that and was like my
heavens adri an I mean God forbid
something ever happens to her there are
going to be so many
suspects that is a crime scene of a
mouth detectives are going to be like
was she killed by a
village what happened here it's just not
wise but I am fascinated by her as a
person I listened to her on a podcast
where she said that on a different trip
to the dentist she had the dentist file
down her back mullers so that she could
make room for bigger things
yeah really took the bumpers off the
bowling
lane and I heard that and was like what
a commitment cheed the
craft I mean I'm not even willing to
wear heels up here for you
folks she's out there changing her
dental records good Christ what a
go-getter
I told that joke in Grand Rapids a few
months
ago where nothing good ever happens and
um there was a dentist in the crowd and
she was blackout drunk and she starts
shouting she goes we can tell we can
tell when somebody's in
porn and I was like well none of us are
going to be able to move on with our
lives until you tell
us floor is yours okay
you have hijacked the show and she goes
they have suction on the roof of their
mouth I was like like the ghost of a
[\h__\h] what are you talking about that
is so not how I thought you would be
able to tell right I thought she was
going to say that when they put the
little vacuum hose in there that the
person's like like hey hey hey hey hey
quit
that you swallow out your work not
here
Goblin I know that I have to have some
daddy issues because my boyfriend's name
is
Chad the sounds of
disapproval yeah you don't date a Chad
unless you come from Deep white
trash I I think it's very ironic as a
comedian that I'm dating a Chad because
Comics we've made fun of dudes with that
name our entire careers like a comedian
dating a Chad is like a store manager
dating a
Karen it makes no sense and I've had a
lot of first with him in our
relationship I mentioned on my special
The Hustler that he's the first guy I've
ever been with who has had a vasectomy
so I had no idea what to expect the
first time he finished I was like is it
going to be
[Music]
[Applause]
dust like when you blow into a Nintendo
cartridge it's
like
nice I had no idea what was going to
happen so I decided to do some research
in a lab called my mouth
and you're welcome we're all adults
here and I'm happy to report my findings
that I believe it's essentially diet
come if I may be so
bold and I have been pretty shocked now
at how many people come up to me after
shows and go you got to make merch that
says diet come
and I'm like who would wear
that make some noise if you think you
would genuinely wear a diet come
shirt oh my God liar
liar you work from
home no HR in your
life no
way and Chad has a 19-year-old daughter
and I wanted her to like me so badly but
I posted that vasectomy joke on
Instagram yeah stepmom up the
air and I forgot that she followed me on
there so later that night she texted
Chad and said hey not trying to start
any
[Laughter]
[\h__\h] but just thought you should know I
definitely unfollowed your girlfriend
today and I thought well it's probably a
good idea because I bet I'm going to
post the joke that I'm currently telling
you guys and I don't think she's going
to like this one
either by the way I don't blame her at
all for unfollowing me I totally get it
I was just bummed because I was hoping
that Instagram was going to be how I
could connect with this teenage girl you
know like before I met her my friends
were like oh don't be nervous she's
going to love you she's going to think
it's so cool that your videos get a
bunch of views and I was like
Oh you mean the one about me blowing her
[Laughter]
dad I don't exactly think she's walking
into her College cafeteria like you guys
it's my dad she
blows you
guys it's like my daddy issues are now
giving other girls daddy
issues it's like a Russian nesting doll
of
[\h__\h] break the
cycle I feel like I should know more
about things like vasectomies because I
don't know if you guys had this in high
school we could get voted you know best
dressed or most athletic but I had that
in middle school and when I was in
seventh grade I got voted most likely to
become a sex head teacher
[Music]
and I look back and I'm like what was I
saying to my
peers at age 12 that made them
collectively go she knows where the
taint
is I should not have won that award I
knew nothing I was such a late bloomer
in every way I didn't start my period
until the last week of 8th grade which
coincided with my school's graduation
trip to the
lake yeah buckle
up and the first time you get a period
they always tell girls oh don't use a
tampon wear a pad so all my friends are
in their cute little bikinis in front of
the boys for the first time I am wearing
a t-shirt and giant men's and one
basketball
shorts trying to hide the outline of
this massive pad
which went from belly button to middle
of my
back it was like wearing a horse
sdle casually at the
beach and then everybody jumped in the
lake and nobody told me that you can't
get in with a pat
on so I jumped in and that thing started
dragging me to in the bottom of the lake
I was like no no no no no no
no my life flashed before my
eyes this thing got so heavy so fast you
could see the water level of the lake
just slowly going lower and lower and
[Applause]
lower and I'm a terrible swimmer I death
gripped on to a front shoulder she was
like what are you doing I was like I'm
bleeding and drowning
please
help so people flopped me up onto the
dock and I stood up and in front of
every boy in my grade 20 gallons of
water dumped out of my
shorts for 40 straight
seconds like the world's grossest
magician
oh that's still going okay
well and that is how you don't get
fingered until your senior
year true
story I feel like all the boys in my
grade we're like we've heard that wet is
good
but that seems too
wet I don't think there's supposed to be
fish coming out
there sort of weird mermaid
lady I got an IUD in recently because I
heard that they could just make your
period go away but the procedure is a
nightmare they basically shove a Lego in
your uterus while you're wide awake I
thought for sure I was going to get
knocked out for this the doctor was like
no I was
like okay well what do you guys do for
the pain she's like oh take a Tylen I'll
Make A
Wish I'm like oh I wish you'd go [\h__\h]
yourself
if you're comfortable sharing Make Some
Noise if you have an
IUD oh my God give these women a key to
the city all right there are Avengers
sitting amongst you tonight it is insane
but I think the thing that's maybe more
traumatizing than that procedure is that
when you get there they ask you to give
a urine sample and women dread giving
urine samples for dudes you guys just
whip your dong out you aim in fire you
could probably do it blindfolded
women giving a urine sample is like
trying to get the leash out from under
the dog's leg on a
walk you're like okay this way maybe
this
way well am I going or you going well
God damn
it so many legs
because women only pee straight for two
of the 20
seconds we PE the rest of the time it
looks like somebody just poked a hole in
a Capri Sun and then started stepping on
it you're
like well
or sideways what me being
sideways I don't even have a hole
there and then a doctor walks in with a
thimble and is like catch
it catch
it I'm like you catch it this is a Twan
job at
least this thing is the same size as a
to-go Ranch container
I can't possibly catch it in this do you
have a Crock-Pot back
there something with handles a wide
birth I can work with
perhaps and a lot of the time you don't
know you're going to have to give a
urine sample so you peed right before
you left the house and then you're in
there trying to squeegee out five
drops you don't have enough pressure in
your stream for it to go out so you just
get a Babbling
Brook that hugs your
body and drops off a butt cheek in the
back have to drop a pin on GPS know
where that [\h__\h] went I have no idea I
can't see back there can't catch
[Music]
that so I'm in there I try to get a
urine sample it's a complete disaster as
always I get nothing in the cup I just
peel over my own wrist like a
child the whole thing stressed me out so
much I had explosive
diarrhea I walked out of there up to the
nurse I was like well didn't get a UR
and Sample but the cup is
full test what you can I
guess it's a broken system it's not my
fault you fix
it and then you lay back and they do the
procedure and an IUD can stay in you for
eight years so after they're done the
nurse hands you a sticker with a date on
it of eight years from that day so you
know when to replace it so I just pop
that on my windshield next to my oil
change sticker
[Applause]
where else am I going to put that thing
I got one that says Valene one that says
voline I just
look just keep an
eye I told my dad about the sticker
thing and he goes oh that's interesting
I wonder if it works the same way as a
car where goes by either the date or the
mileage
[Music]
I was like shut your mouth dad I mean
I'm definitely going to use it on stage
but shut your
mouth sicko we're not friends I don't
want to joke with you like that you're
going to make me start an only fans who
keep that [\h__\h] up shut
up that's definitely not how it works by
the way that'd be very funny to me if
they were secretly putting tiny
odometers
you go in for a check at the doctor's
like somebody had a busy April Jesus
Christ no way this thing's lasting eight
years you're burning the tires clean off
this thing slow
down I'm very happy to be living with
Chad I lived alone for a few years after
the divorce I feel like if you live
alone for too long you start to become
feral Make Some Noise if you live alone
right
now all right so that's 12 people
who showered for the first time
tonight good for you I am honored to be
the reason you would bathe and leave
your
home because you don't have to do
anything when you live alone there's
nobody around to judge you and you start
to act like you were raised by wolves
right I watched myself do something so
unhinged at one point I don't know if
you guys have it in your shower where if
the water's been hitting the shower
curtain for a long time it starts to get
kind of discolored at the bottom I tried
cleaning it it wouldn't come off and
instead of just going and buying a new
shower curtain like a normal person I
just sat in my bathtub with scissors and
I just cut the
bottom I just went full meth head I was
just
like hearts and crafts hearts and crafts
I literally gave my shower
bangs it's not a mentally stable place
to be
in and then of course it really looked
like [\h__\h] so I went to Target and they
had just released fall candles and I
learned that day that if you smell
candles for 30 minutes straight you will
accidentally get a little [\h__\h]
high nothing crazy but I'm a lightweight
and nobody in the Dare program talk to
me about
candles so I was unprepared for what
happened to my body so I was floating
around Target I grabbed the shower
curtain I wanted and when I went home
and hung it up it only stretched like
half the length of my shower and it was
so long five extra feet of fabric coming
off the bottom of this
thing and my steps sister came over the
next day and she used my bathroom and
she came out and she goes why do you
have a window curtain in there
I was like what
now she goes that's a window curtain you
didn't think it was weird that when you
hung it up there was an entire Met gala
ball gown coming off of
it I was like I accidentally got [\h__\h]
up on pumpkin spice and I blocked out I
don't want to talk about
it but it's fine I can fix this and I
grab my scissors and I just cut the
bottom we're
fine I can feel that I'm starting to get
a little too comfortable with Chad now
that we live together you know in the
beginning you try so hard you care what
you look like I'd go get Brazilian waxes
all the time now I'm just trying to not
scare kids at the
pool it's a different level of effort
I'm willing to put in now I just tell my
Wax Lady the same thing that Chad tells
the guy who trims his beard I'm just
like take a little off the sides Be
Careful around the
lips let's not get
crazy I am pretty shocked at the links
that young girls now are willing to go
to to attract boys I don't know if you
guys have heard of this trend through
Tik Tok called
vabbing okay I just found out about this
apparently some teenage girls now before
they leave the house are sticking their
fingers down there and then wiping it on
their
neck to try to use their pheromones to
attract
boys the confidence of gen Z is so
[\h__\h]
wild and truly
Disturbed I mean cold day in hell that
you would catch a millennial or older
wiping anything from this area on their
neck like godamn
popery that was so not the message
taught to us about this area by our
elders right they were like hey lock up
your shame go yeah okay yeah okay we
didn't even want anybody to know we had
a
vagina we were just walking through
Middle School like okay conceal and
carry okay nobody see it nobody smell it
just spraying 17 pumps of Bath & Body
Works cucumber
melon smell like every lift driver's
car just
Insanity yeah our sex headed teachers
didn't talk to us about this area like
it was hot
sauce they weren't like Hey Y'all it's
good on
everything get it out
there no they talked to us about it like
it was black licorice
they were like hey not everybody's going
to like
that
okay you stay humble yeah yeah yeah okay
sure and we did we're a humble
generation anybody here have a teenage
[Applause]
daughter well don't smell their neck
[Laughter]
now that is not lip
gloss sounds like a town hall meeting in
here guys like oh hey
this is an
outrage I feel like there might be some
interesting phone calls on the drive
home
tonight put your [\h__\h] sister on
I do actually want to try and keep the
magic alive with Chad for as long as I
can and my ex and I got pretty gross
together toward the end he and I always
lived in a place that only had one
bathroom and he would go in there and
take 45 minute man
shits and I finally asked him I was like
hey why does it take you so long to do
that and he goes well my doctor told me
that it's bad to push so I don't
push I just sit and I let it fall
out I was like what are you a
geisha what are you trying to take these
dainty shits for you're a man just grab
onto something fire it out get the [\h__\h]
out of
there we can't wait for the stars to
align
Mulan Sunday we got errands to run go
get out
so he went in there one day for one of
his
sessions and I knew it was going to be a
session cuz I could hear him lock the
door which he always only did for number
two and I didn't know why I think I know
now I think you dudes have this poo
phobia that while you're sitting there
all
vulnerable you're afraid we're going to
like bust the door down and jump on your
lap and start tickling you
I'm not steo why would I do
that I would never do
that so he's in there door locked and on
this day our buttholes had
sned and I was like oh
no because I have IBS so when I got to
go I got to go so I texted him and I was
like hey I'm about to [\h__\h] my
pants siren
Emoji fire
Emoji making it Crystal Clear he doesn't
respond I can hear his phone get my text
and I hear him just swipe out of it and
continue to watch parks and wreck I'm
like you
[\h__\h] so now I realize I do not
have access to a toilet and I've got
some demons coming down the
shoot I am in apocalypse survival mode
so I start frantically looking around
our apartment for a substitute
toilet the first thing I see is the
kitchen
sink I know right away I was like
too
high it's a lot of gymnastics I'm not
qualified
for next thing I see is my ex's favorite
hat which emotionally felt like the
right
choice cuz I was ready to soft serve him
some pipe and hot
justice but I was like o that's a small
surface area I'm not confident in the
AIM you guys know how I feel about urine
samples it's like if you can't be in a
cup you can't poop in a
hat that's a Dr Seuss book we all grew
up
with everybody knows you can't do
that and so I looked and I looked and I
had to [\h__\h] in an empty cardboard Amazon
box in my own living room like an old
homeless
man that changes you as a
person I was just squatting and crying
our cats walked up to
me and booped
noses I was like get out of here go they
just watched me from the corner with
giant
eyes they were just looking at me like
oh you are one of
us
neat and after I was done I told my
friends what had happened and they were
all like why don't you just poop in your
cat's litter
box and I was like cuz I'm not trying to
dominate them for the rest of their
lives do you understand what a deranged
power move that would be
to just bring the heat like
that just dunk on
them that would be like if you [\h__\h] in
your baby's
diaper your child would be taken from
You There are rules to this
life but I tell you guys this to tell
you I've been trying to hide that
version of me far away from Chad I don't
ever want Chad to meet gross Kelsey
right
in warehouses you know they have those
signs it's like 32 days since last
workplace
incident well I have a tiny one in my
heart that says
1,842 days since I [\h__\h] in a
[Applause]
box I'm trying to keep that number very
high but when Chad and I moved in
together last year we celebrated we went
out we drank a bunch of tequila and then
the next morning I got
chipotle bad choices and we went back to
our new place and I went into one of the
bathrooms to do my business but it's a
new bathroom to me so I turned on what I
thought was the fan turns out it was the
heater that's not what you want
[Music]
that takes a normal number two smell and
turns it into a Woodstock 99 porta
potty immediately I I'm in there
sweating and panicking I'm like oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] and I finish up and I walk out
and I close the door behind me which is
the universal sign for give it a sec
no one needs to go in here for the next
2 to 49
hours change your plans change your
route Chad completely ignores this major
sign that I'm throwing up at him he just
blows right by me and walks in there to
get a
Kleenex my brain in slow-mo was like
don't go in
[Applause]
there and he came out and I was
like um I am so
sorry could you smell
[Music]
things and he goes I couldn't smell
anything you're fine and I was like oh
thank
God you might want to take a covid test
actually don't waste a test you have
Co my [\h__\h] was the test and you
failed and that's when Chad goes I'm
just kidding I could totally smell that
do you see the tears streaming down my
face godamn it
so something I've learned is that a lot
of people don't realize that comedians
know how to not be comedians off stage
like some people just think we're always
set to clown mode or something because a
few years ago my mom got sick and she
was in the hospital for part of the time
and 3 weeks in her doctor turns to me
and goes so I heard you're a comedian
and I was like yeah I am he goes oh just
surprises me cuz I don't really get a
funny vibe from you
and I was like well my mom's still in
the hospital after 3 weeks so I'm not
really getting a great doctor
Vibe I can be Petty off the clock too
[\h__\h] I will do it for
free also what does a funny vibe look
like to this guy we're in a hospital you
think I'm going to walk through the
waiting room honking boobs like he he he
he people are bleeding out you got to
clock out
sometimes but here's the thing when my
mom was in the hospital she ended up
getting diagnosed with dementia which
has of course been the most
heartbreaking thing to go through but
she is so smart and so funny that even
with dementia she's still pretty crafty
like still tries to prank
people so she and my brother were
talking he thought it was going well and
then all of a sudden she just starts
shouting
nurse
nurse and my brother's like oh my God
Mom I'm right here what do you need the
nurses come running in they're like
Kathy oh my God what's going on and my
mom just goes look how handsome my son
[Laughter]
is like are you out of your [\h__\h] mind
you can not be the mom who cried hot
sun you're going to get kicked out of
the home cuz now I feel like next time
she actually needs help the nurse is
just going to pop her head around from
50 feet away and be like oh let me guess
Kathy is your daughter
funny is that what you're screaming at
us for it'd be so great if she was like
she's
okay don't really get a funny vibe from
her want some apple
juice I have to tell you guys something
that just happened my cousin and I
visited my mom and we thought that my
mom had fallen asleep so my cousin
decided to tell me that she just took
her two High School nieces out to dinner
and her nieces are obsessed with mukbang
videos you guys know what mukbang videos
are okay if you don't know it's this big
trend on YouTube people order massive
quantities of food and they eat them on
camera so her nieces love these mukbang
videos and they're at dinner and one of
her nieces cleans her plate so fast and
my cousin looks at her and goes wow
Bailey you should do your own Bucky
videos
and her niece went white in the
face which is very funny if you know
what [\h__\h] is
remember that 0.12 resting blood
alcohol
talking such a delayed
reaction whole
book yeah I can also tell that some of
you do not know what [\h__\h] is and
honestly you're better people for it you
are more pure of heart okay a Midwest
mom just went
if you want to find out what it is give
it a Google later um don't do it at work
you'll get
fired it is a finishing
move in the world of
porn and I'm like dying laughing at this
story and then all of a sudden my mom
goes I've done bucki once
and my cousin and I were like no no no
no
no do not say that word in the
home I promise it is not whatever you
think it
is it's not some Fitness class you took
at the
YMCA I'm sure my mom was just sitting
there listening like oh well Zumba was
full that one day so I think I popped
over to [\h__\h] it's like no you did not
no you did not
nope you never did
that and here's the thing I always take
really good care of my mom but I took
extra good care of her that day because
I was like those cannot be your last
[Applause]
words don't you
dare and this is is strange but my
entire family and I including my mom are
actually world champion foosball
players yeah thank
you and my mom is in the Foosball Hall
of
Fame yeah but every time my mom gets a
new nurse the nurse will always ask her
about her life and my mom always goes
well I'm in the fooseball Hall of
Fame and every nurse goes uh sure you
[Music]
are and I'm always standing there like
oh yeah no I know that sounds made up
but I swear it's real and and the nurse
is like hey you don't have
to and I'm like lady I swear to God I
can show you her trophies I can show you
video of her plane and that's when the
nurse starts to look at the other nurses
like oh does the daughter have dementia
too it's like a T-Mobile family plan of
dementia too weird to believe and my mom
growing up was also somebody you did not
want to cross my parents got divorced in
the 90s back when there were home phone
answering
machines and before the divorce our
answering machine message was my dad
saying you've reached the cooks please
leave us a message and then after the
divorce my mom had changed it to her
just blasting alism aets you ought to
know so every time my dad would call my
mom would let it go to the machine so
that if he wanted to leave a message for
her every time he first had to sit
through the lyrics and I'm here to
remind you of the mess you left when you
went away
[Laughter]
I mean that's a bad [\h__\h] move right
there that takes balls cuz it's not like
that was just the message for when my
dad
called that was the message for
literally anybody who called our house
so after a while we started get messages
from people like
hey this is Dave from
Blockbuster and uh I'm here to remind
you your space jam VHS is overdue
really sorry about whatever you're going
through and long before my mom had
dementia she had retired from teaching
and she had taken on some interesting
retirement Hobbies she had started to
screenshot the Selfies I would post on
Instagram and then she would print them
out and go to Kohl's and buy those 30
photos collage
frames and frame my
selfies but I didn't know she was doing
this until I visited home one day and I
just walked into a
[Laughter]
[Music]
museum of my
narcissism and my mom crept up behind me
she was like
do you love
it what is this a haunted house this is
[\h__\h] horrifying I'll never take a
selfie again this is like an
intervention but here's the thing nobody
had taught my mom how to crop a
screenshot so all of these printed
framed photos show her phone battery
percentage if somebody texted her as she
took the
screenshot it's up there there's a frame
photo somewhere of my face with a text
from my ex to my mom like your daughter
just [\h__\h] in a box
please
advise so I decided last year that I
didn't want to have kids and it was so
weird because a few months later I
started to get really bad cramps and
they did an ultrasound and they found a
pop in my uterus which is like a skin
tag and I think it's so crazy that the
human instinct to reproduce is so strong
that as soon as I said I'm not having
kids my uterus was like hm [\h__\h] we're
growing
something you have been zero
help you keep feeding me Diet
come just hangs out and here makes the
floor
[Laughter]
sticky the IUD doesn't know what to do
do with it Chad's had a vasectomy so
there's nothing to
defend it's like two goalies on a soccer
field with no other
players all right Madison you guys have
been [\h__\h] incredible thank you so
much
[Applause]
[Music]
by the way I say I'm trying to keep the
magic alive with him and then also this
morning I said to him I wipe too hard
and my butt crack
hurts he's like oh wow I really feel the
magic yeah that's that's
palpable that probably won't stay in the
special but you know I just thought I'd
just thought I'd share my morning with
you fine
folks be
[Music]
h